https://www.signaturehardware.com/privacy-policy/#CCPA

0
You have no items in your shopping cart.
BathroomBackShop All BathroomBathtubsClawfoot TubsFreestanding TubsAcrylic TubsJapanese Soaking TubsCopper TubsCast Iron TubsSolid Surface TubsStainless Steel TubsStone TubsSlipper TubsPainted TubsAlcove BathtubsDrop-in TubsAll BathtubsBathroom VanitiesDouble Sink VanitiesVessel Sink VanitiesSemi-Recessed Sink VanitiesUndermount Sink VanitiesTeak VanitiesMahogany VanitiesWood VanitiesConsole VanitiesNarrow VanitiesVanity TopsAll Bathroom VanitiesBathroom SinksPedestal SinksConsole SinksVessel SinksUndermount Bathroom SinksDrop-in SinksSemi-Recessed SinksWall-Mount SinksCorner SinksAll Bathroom SinksBathroom Sink FaucetsWidespread Faucets4" Centerset FaucetsSingle-Hole FaucetsVessel Sink FaucetsBridge Bathroom FaucetsWall-Mount FaucetsModern FaucetsWaterfall FaucetsNon-Mixing FaucetsAll Bathroom Sink FaucetsTub FaucetsFreestanding Tub FaucetsRoman Tub FaucetsTub Mounted FaucetsWall-Mount Tub FaucetsTub Faucet SetsTub SpoutsAll Tub FaucetsShowersShower Systems and FaucetsRain ShowersShower Heads and ArmsExposed Pipe ShowersShower PanelsClawfoot Tub Shower KitsShower PansHand Showers and Slide BarsShower Diverters and ValvesShower Body JetsAll ShowersMedicine CabinetsRecessed Medicine CabinetsSurface Mount CabinetsCorner Medicine CabinetsAll Medicine CabinetsBathroom MirrorsFrameless MirrorsFramed MirrorsLED-Lighted Vanity MirrorsPivot MirrorsLighted Makeup MirrorsAll Bathroom MirrorsToilets and BidetsTwo-Piece ToiletsOne-Piece ToiletsRear Outlet ToiletsHigh Tank ToiletsADA Compliant ToiletsHigh Efficiency ToiletsSiphonic ToiletsBidetsToilet SeatsToilet PartsAll Toilets and BidetsShower Curtain RodsCurved Shower RodsStraight Shower RodsD-Shaped Shower RodsL-Shaped Shower RodsNeo Angle Shower RodsOval Shower RodsRectangular Shower RodsRound Shower RodsU-Shaped Shower RodsShower Rod SupportsClawfoot Shower RodsShower Curtain Rod PartsAll Shower Curtain RodsShower Curtains and HooksHook Free Shower CurtainsFabric Shower CurtainsVinyl Shower CurtainsShower Curtain RingsAll Shower Curtains and HooksBathroom AccessoriesClawfoot Tub AccessoriesTowel HoldersRobe HooksBathroom ShelvesWood Bath MatsShower CaddiesBathroom Hardware SetsToilet Paper HoldersToilet BrushesSoap Dishes and DispensersToothbrush and Tumbler HoldersGrab BarsLinen CabinetsLaundry HampersBath PillowsBathtub and Spa StepsKitchen and Bath CleanersAll Bathroom AccessoriesShower and Tub DrainsLinear Shower DrainsShower Drain CoversShower DrainsTub Overflow DrainsTub DrainsAll Shower and Tub DrainsPlumbing Parts & SuppliesStops and Shut Off ValvesP Traps and S TrapsTub and Shower PartsFaucet HandlesBathroom Sink DrainsEscutcheons and FlangesTub Water SuppliesSink Water SuppliesAll Plumbing Parts & Supplies
KitchenBackShop All KitchenFarmhouse SinksFireclay Farmhouse SinksCopper Farmhouse SinksStone Farmhouse SinksStainless Farmhouse SinksCast Iron Farmhouse SinksRetrofit Farmhouse SinksAll Farmhouse SinksKitchen SinksCopper Kitchen SinksCast Iron Kitchen SinksGranite Composite SinksStainless Steel Kitchen SinksDrainboard Kitchen SinksDrop-In Kitchen SinksUndermount Kitchen SinksAll Kitchen SinksBar and Prep SinksCopper Bar SinksStainless Steel Bar SinksFireclay Bar SinksMarble Bar SinksWhiskey Barrel Bar SinksAll Bar and Prep SinksKitchen FaucetsSingle-Hole FaucetsWidespread FaucetsWall-Mount FaucetsKitchen Bridge FaucetsPot FillersBar FaucetsWater DispensersSensor FaucetsPull-Down FaucetsPull-Out FaucetsSpring-Spout FaucetsAll Kitchen FaucetsKitchen Soap DispensersKitchen DrainsKitchen Sink DrainsKitchen PlumbingGarbage DisposalsBar Sink DrainsAll Kitchen DrainsUtility SinksUtility Sink Faucets
HardwareBackShop All HardwareRegistersFloor RegistersWall RegistersRadiator Flanges and KeysAll RegistersDoor Handles and LocksEntry Door and Lock SetsInterior Door Knob SetsDeadbolt Locks and SetsScreen Door LatchesRim Lock SetsMortise Lock SetsAll Door Handles and LocksBarn Door and Gate HardwareDoor PullsDoor Latches and HaspsSlide Bolts and PadlocksGate HardwareBarn Door HardwareSliding Barn DoorsMini Barn Door HardwareAll Barn Door and Gate HardwarePocket Door HardwarePocket Door PullsPocket Door LocksAll Pocket Door HardwareDoor Hinges and StrapsStrap HingesScreen Door HingesMortise HingesPintle HingesAll Door Hinges and StrapsDoor AccessoriesDoor StopsClavosPush PlatesKeyhole CoversAll Door AccessoriesDoor KnockersTraditional Door KnockersModern Door KnockersNovelty Door KnockersBrass Door KnockersBronze Door KnockersIron Door KnockersAll Door KnockersCoat Hooks and RacksCoat HooksCoat RacksAll Coat Hooks and RacksShelf BracketsBrass Shelf BracketsIron Shelf BracketsBronze Shelf BracketsAll Shelf BracketsCabinet and Drawer HardwareCabinet KnobsDrawer PullsCup PullsCabinet Latches and HingesAll Cabinet and Drawer HardwareAppliance PullsCremone BoltsWindow Cremone BoltsDoor Cremone BoltsCabinet Cremone BoltsAll Cremone BoltsWindow HardwareWindow Sash HardwareShutter HardwareAll Window Hardware
LightingBackShop All LightingChandeliersCrystal ChandeliersMetal ChandeliersModern ChandeliersRustic ChandeliersIndustrial ChandeliersTraditional ChandeliersGlam ChandeliersRectangular ChandeliersRound ChandeliersLinear ChandeliersGeometric ChandeliersLED ChandeliersAll ChandeliersPendant LightsGlass Pendant LightsMetal Pendant LightsModern Pendant LightsRustic Pendant LightsIndustrial Pendant LightsGlam Pendant LightsBronze Pendant LightsBlack Pendant LightsSilver Pendant LightsGold Pendant LightsNickel Pendant LightsLED Pendant LightsAll Pendant LightsFlush-Mount Ceiling LightsSemi-Flush-Mount LightingGlass Flush-Mount LightsMetal Flush-Mount LightsModern Flush-Mount LightsIndustrial Flush-Mount LightsBlack Flush-Mount LightsBrass Flush-Mount LightsBronze Flush-Mount LightsSilver Flush-Mount LightsNickel Flush-Mount LightsAll Flush-Mount Ceiling LightsWall SconcesCandle Wall SconcesModern Wall SconcesTraditional Wall SconcesGlam Wall SconcesBlack Wall SconcesBrass Wall SconcesGold Wall SconcesBrushed Nickel Wall SconcesBronze Wall SconcesNickel Wall SconcesAll Wall SconcesOutdoor LightingOutdoor Wall Sconce LightsOutdoor Lamp Post LightsOutdoor Hanging PendantsOutdoor Flush-Mount LightsModern Outdoor LightsTraditional Outdoor LightsIndustrial Outdoor LightsOutdoor LED LightsAll Outdoor LightingBathroom Vanity LightingVanity Sconces2-Light Vanity Lights3-Light Vanity Lights4-Light Vanity LightsModern Vanity LightsRustic Vanity LightsIndustrial Vanity LightsGlam Vanity LightsLED Vanity LightsAll Bathroom Vanity Lighting
OutdoorBackShop All OutdoorMailboxes and SlotsMailbox AccessoriesAll Mailboxes and SlotsOutdoor FaucetsOutdoor ShowersWall-Mount ShowersFreestanding ShowersShower DrainsAll Outdoor Showers
CollectionsBackEdison CollectionPinecrest CollectionBeasley CollectionBoca Raton CollectionHibiscus CollectionPendleton CollectionProvincetown CollectionVilamonte CollectionGreyfield CollectionCarraway CollectionSt. Augustine Collection Key West Collection Sitka CollectionEdenton CollectionRigi CollectionCooper CollectionExira CollectionPagosa Collection Rotunda Collection
InspirationBackMy Signature StyleLookbook Buying GuidesBathroomKitchenHardwareHome AccentsAll Buying GuidesHow-To GuidesBathroomKitchenHardwareHome AccentsAll How-To GuidesDesigner SpotlightsCasa MamiOak Design ProjectZosia Mamet & Evan JonigkeitAll Designer SpotlightsIdeas & InspirationBathroomKitchenHardwareHome AccentsAll Ideas & InspirationHow-To VideosShop by Room Shop by KitchenShop by BathroomShop by Powder RoomShop by Laundry RoomAll Shop by Room
My Wish List
Log In
Sign Up
Find A Showroom
Customer Service
Help Center
Returns
Track My Package
Privacy & Security
Your privacy is important. At SignatureHardware.com, we pledge to never sell, trade, rent, or otherwise transmit any personally identifiable information about you to any third party without first receiving your permission.
Privacy and Security Policy
SignatureHardware.com will not be held liable for any loss, damage, or other claim arising as a result of your use of this site. All SignatureHardware.com services, content, and technology provided in association with the SignatureHardware.com site are provided "as is," without warranties of any kind.
To the full extent permissible by applicable law and except as specifically set forth herein, neither signaturehardware.com nor signaturehardware.com's licensors make any warranties or representations of any kind with respect to the SignatureHardware.com services, content, technology, or products that SignatureHardware.com or its licensors expressly disclaim all implied and express warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or noninfringement with respect to the same.
Without limiting the foregoing, no warranty is given that the SignatureHardware.com service or technology is error-free. SignatureHardware.com and its licensors disclaim any warranty of title or any other warranties for any third party's offering(s) or product(s).
Data Security
Signature Hardware uses 128 bit SSL encryption to help protect your personal information online and uses 3rd party verification to audit our site security. Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only employees and authorized agents who need access to your personal information to perform a specific job are granted access to your personal information.
Email Communications
We may contact you via email to send you necessary transaction-related messages, such as order confirmation and shipment confirmation notices, or to respond to customer inquiries.
We may also send you newsletters and additional email messages about our products, services, contests, and promotions that we feel may be of interest to you. If you no longer wish to receive these and other promotional communications from us, you may select the unsubscribe link which is present in each email.
Collection of Information
We collect information from our customers in order to enhance customer service, create a more personalized shopping experience, and improve the website. We collect personal information such as, but not limited to, email address, name, and postal address only when provided to us to place an order, sign up to receive emails, or otherwise interact or communicate with us via our website, on other websites, via phone, or in person. This information is used to process and validate your order, provide customer support, keep record of your purchase history, and for other transaction and account-related activities.
This site may also collect non-personally identifiable information via cookies or web beacons from your browser automatically in order to collect information about site traffic, improve website speed, save shopping carts, provide security badges, customize advertising, and connect with third-party web services. Cookies used on this site do not and cannot gather personal data on a user's hard drive. You may opt-out of third party advertising cookies at any time by visiting www.networkadvertising.org/choices. You may also delete cookies from your browser at any time. Some website functionality, such as the ability to save items in your shopping cart, may be impacted by the deletion of cookies.
We respect children’s privacy. We do not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information from children under age 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any personal information to us, and rely on a parent or guardian to assist you.
Do Not Track Information
Some browsers have a “Do Not Track” feature that lets you tell websites that you do not want to have your online activities tracked. This feature can be found in your browser’s privacy settings. Enabling/disabling the Do Not Track feature in your browser does not ensure that all websites you visit will respond to the request. SignatureHardware.com does not respond to Do Not Track signals at this time. Third-party advertisers on SignatureHardware.com may or may not respond to these requests.
Rights in Your Personal Information
Subject to our legal requirements and business purposes, you may be able to exercise the following rights in your personal information:
•	That we provide you with the personal information we have collected about you in the preceding twelve months. We will aim to provide this information to you, free of charge, in a commonly used electronic file format.
•	That we delete certain personal information we have collected about you. There may be instances where we retain some personal information as necessary to comply with our legal and business obligations.
•	That we disclose the categories of personal information we collect, the sources from which we collect personal information, the purposes for which we collect personal information, the third parties with whom we share personal information, and the third parties to whom we sell personal information. This information will always be provided in this Privacy Policy, and we will update this Privacy Policy as necessary to accurately reflect how we are using your information. You can see when this Privacy Statement was last updated in the “Last Updated” section below.
California Residents' Rights to Personal Information
As a resident of California, you have the right to request from businesses a disclosure of data collection and sales practices in connection with your data. This includes: categories of personal information collected, the source of the information, use of the information and — if the information was disclosed or sold to third parties — the categories of personal information disclosed or sold to third parties and the categories of third parties to whom such information was disclosed or sold. Learn more about California Privacy Laws at the Office of the Attorney General website.
As a California Resident, you are afforded:
•	The right to request a copy of the specific personal information collected about you during the 12 months before your request (together with a general “personal information request”)
•	The right to have such information deleted (with exceptions)
•	The right to request that your personal information not be sold to third parties, if applicable
•	The right not to be discriminated against because you exercised any of these rights.
How to Exercise Your Rights Regarding Your Personal Information
You may request a disclosure report regarding your personal information, request that your personal information be deleted from our database, and/or opt out of marketing communications by completing and submitting the Data Subject Access Request Form. Please note, we take security measures to identify our consumers to a reasonable degree of certainty prior to providing any information or processing requests.
Legal Disclosures
We may share information with law enforcement officials, governmental agencies in response to requests for subpoenas, court order, or if we are otherwise required to provide such information by law. We may also share personal information to other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation in order to protect against actual fraud, potential fraud, or unauthorized transactions, or where it is necessary to protect our legal rights, enforce website policies and agreements, or to protect ourselves or others.
We may disclose such information in response to requests from law enforcement officials conducting investigations; subpoenas; a court order; or if we are otherwise required to disclose such information by law. We also will release personal information where disclosure is necessary to protect our legal rights, enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements, or to protect ourselves or others. For example, we may share information to reduce the risk of fraud or if someone uses or attempts to use the Site for illegal reasons or to commit fraud.
Conditions of Use
This privacy policy applies to the SignatureHardware.com site. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices on any web site not operated by Signature Hardware, to which the site links or that links to the site.
SignatureHardware.com will not be held liable for any loss, damage, or other claim arising as a result of your use of this site. All SignatureHardware.com services, content, and technology provided in association with the SignatureHardware.com site are provided "as is," without warranties of any kind. To the full extent permissible by applicable law and except as specifically set forth herein, neither signaturehardware.com nor signaturehardware.com's licensors make any warranties or representations of any kind with respect to the SignatureHardware.com services, content, technology, or products that SignatureHardware.com or its licensors expressly disclaim all implied and express warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or noninfringement with respect to the same. Without limiting the foregoing, no warranty is given that the SignatureHardware.com service or technology is error-free. SignatureHardware.com and its licensors disclaim any warranty of title or any other warranties for any third party's offering(s) or product(s).
Questions? Customer Service is happy to assist you.support@signaturehardware.com
Our Promise to You
Warranty Details
Return Policy
Design Inspiration Delivered Straight to Your Inbox.Subscribe Now.
Please wait, loading...
This site is protected by reCAPTCHA and the Google Privacy Policy and Terms of Service apply.
You are using an outdated browser. Some features of this website may require a newer version to operate.
